zedomax.com 2014-06-17

# Privacy | zedomax.com

## Purpose and Scope

This policy discloses what information we gather about you when you visit any of our web sites (all zedomax.com and affiliated network sites) or buy product directly from us. It describes how we use that information and how you can control it.

## Information Zedomax Network LLC gathers and tracks

## Personal information

We use the personal information you provide voluntarily to send information youâ€™ve requested and to fulfill orders. The specific use of your personal information varies, depending on how you contact us:
We never sell or rent your email address or other personally identifiable information you provide us under these circumstances.
With third parties we retain to perform functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders,Â are restricted from using your information for any other purpose.
We do not rent or sell our email lists.
We release personal information when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Zedomax.com, our users, or others. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Aggregated tracking information

We analyze visitorsâ€™ use of our sites by tracking information such as pageviews, traffic flow, search terms, and click through. We use this information to improve our sites. We also share this anonymous traffic and demographic information in aggregate form with advertisers and other business partners. We do not share any information with advertisers that can identify an individual user.
We use Google, a third party publishing service to monetize our site.Â  Google collects information for more relevant advertising, you can read their [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We use Statcounter, a third party web analytics service to improve our web site performance and user experience. We use this information to improve usability on our sites and to help support our customers online needs. Â Statcounter does not reveal any personally identifiable information, such as names or email address.

For more information on the Statcounter service and privacy policy, please see their [privacy policy](http://my7.statcounter.com/privacy.html).

## Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computerâ€™s hard drive through your web browser when you visit our sites. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your computer, so that we can provide you with personalized information and features. We also use cookies to track user traffic patterns.
On our sites, we and some of our advertisers use a third-party ad server to display ads. These ads may contain cookies. The ad server receives these cookies, and we donâ€™t have access to them.
You can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies or to block cookies. If you block cookies, you may not be able to use certain site features or functions.

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

## Notification of Changes

This privacy policy was put in effect on June 9th, 2009.
If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on zedomax.com. Â If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via email. Users will be able to opt out of any new use of their personal information.

## How to update, correct, or delete your information

Email: To update or unsubscribe from our email newsletters or product announcements,Â  send email to sales zedomax.com.
